http://www.life-enhancement.com/pages/terms-conditions-of-use-for-life-enhancement-com

Most Popular Health Articles
Sign up for our Newsletter Emails!
Most Popular Health Articles
Sign up for our Newsletter Emails!
Disclaimer
The material provided on this site by Life Enhancement Products, Inc. is for educational purposes only and any recommendations are not intended to replace the advice of your physician. Life Enhancement Products, Inc. has made every effort to assure that no inaccurate or misleading information will appear on this web site. The data and opinions appearing in Life Enhancement Magazine are for informational purposes only. Readers are encouraged to seek advice from a competent medical professional regarding the applicability of any recommendations with regard to your symptoms or condition.
The following Terms and Conditions governing the use of Life Enhancement's web site and are designed to protect everyone who uses this site. By using this site you agree to these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions do not use this site. Life Enhancement Products, Inc. has the right to revise and update these Terms and Conditions at anytime without prior notification.
Medical References and Information
The content of Life Enhancement's web site is offered on an informational basis only. No content is intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment.
You should always seek the advice and guidance of a qualified health provider before:
Making any adjustment to any medication or treatment you are currently using.
Stopping any medication or treatment you are currently using.
Starting any new medication or treatment, whether or not it was discussed on Life-Enhancement.Com. Our experts offer their recommendations only as "generally informational" and not as specifically applicable to any individual's medical problem(s), concerns and/or needs.
*NOTE*
It is important that you do not reduce, change, or discontinue any medication or treatment without consulting your physician first. Please note that the brand names mentioned on this web site are registered properties of their manufacturers.
In the event of any medical emergency, call your doctor or your local health emergency service immediately. If you choose to utilize any information provided by Life Enhancement, its editors or any other employees of Life Enhancement Products, Inc., you do so solely at your own risk.
Policy Statement
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. fully guarantees the quality of every product bearing our label. This guarantee certifies that our products are manufactured to meet the highest standards of potency, purity and freshness. If you are not satisfied in every way, return the unused portion within 30 days of receipt, and we will issue you a full credit toward another purchase, or refund 100% of your money. You always keep your six-month subscription to Life Enhancement Magazine, a $29.70 value! (Note: returns do not include shipping costs.)
Privacy Disclosure Statement / Privacy Policy
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses information gathering and usage practices for our web site and for Life Enhancement Magazine.
Life Enhancement does not collect personally identifying information about visitors except when specifically and knowingly provided by visitors.
No visitor's personally identifying information will be used by Life Enhancement Products, Inc. for editorial purposes, unless that information is intentionally provided by the individual as part of a customer testimonial letter or a letter to our experts. When an individual submits a customer testimonial letter or a letter to our experts, Life Enhancement reserves the right to publish the individual's first name, city and state of residence.
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. will not share any personal information with third parties without the permission of the individual. If specifically requested by the visitor, name and address information will be shared with selected businesses for promotional purposes.
Life-Enhancement.Com
This web site, maintained by Life Enhancement, Inc., may place a "cookie" in the browser files of the user's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. The cookie could enable Life Enhancement, Inc. to relate a user's use of this site to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided Life Enhancement Inc.
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. uses order forms for visitors to request information, products and services. Contact information (such as Email addresses, phone numbers, etc.) and billing data (such as account or credit card numbers) are collected and secured for internal use only. Customer account and or credit card numbers are used only to affect billing for products and services ordered by the visitor.
Links to Other Sites
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. does not endorse the content on any third party web sites. Life Enhancement Products, Inc. is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites, sites framed within the Life-Enhancement.Com site, or third party advertisements, and does not make any representations regarding their content or accuracy. Your use of third-party web sites is at your own risk and subject to the Terms and Conditions of use for those sites.
Mailing Lists
From time to time, Life Enhancement Products, Inc. may offer its mailing lists to other companies to offer products or services to customers and may offer its members special promotions or informational literature. Any requests to be removed from the mailing list will be immediately honored without question. Please note that persons requesting removal from the mailing list may receive one additional mailing due to the magazine's publishing schedule. Requests for removal by the first of each month will not receive the following month's mailing.
Mailing List Removal
Life Enhancement Product's web site gives visitors the following options for removing their information from our database, or to discontinue receipt of communications or Life Enhancement Magazine:
Send email to remove@Life-Enhancement.Com
Call our Customer Service Department at 1-800-543-3873
Change / Modify Mailing List Information
This site gives visitors the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:
Send an email to change or modify your information or call our Customer Service Department at 1-800-543-3873.
Contacting Us
Contacting Life Enhancement Products, Inc. if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Life Enhancement Products, Inc., or your dealings with Life Enhancement Products, Inc., you may contact us at: Life Enhancement Products, Inc.
Life Enhancement Products
4900 Mill St. Ste B-32 Reno, NV 89502
Contact us by Phone:
Within the U.S.: 1-800-543-3873
Outside of the U.S.: 1-775-783-1600
Contacting the Web Site if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you may E-Mail us at: info@Life-Enhancement.Com
General
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. is located in Reno, Nevada, USA. Life Enhancement Products, Inc. makes no claims that the content is appropriate or may be downloaded outside of the United States. Access to the content may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access Life-Enhancement.Com from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction. The following provisions survive the expiration or termination of these Terms and Conditions for any reason whatsoever: Liability, User Submissions, Indemnity, Jurisdiction, and Complete Agreement.
Except as expressly provided in a particular "legal notice" on Life-Enhancement.Com, these Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and Life-Enhancement.Com with respect to the use of Life-Enhancement.Com, and content. Your use of Life-Enhancement.Com is also subject to the Life-Enhancement.Com privacy policy.
We hope you find Life-Enhancement.Com helpful and convenient to use! Questions or comments regarding this website should be directed to: info@Life-Enhancement.Com
Use of Content
All content is protected by copyright under United States and foreign laws. All content remains the property of Life Enhancement Products, Inc. and its licensors. Any use of the content not expressly permitted by these Terms and Conditions is a breach of these Terms and Conditions and may violate copyright, trademark, and/or other laws. Content and features are subject to change or termination without notice at the discretion of Life Enhancement Products, Inc. All rights whether expressed or not are reserved by Life Enhancement Products, Inc. and its licensors.
Life Enhancement Products, Inc. authorizes you to make single copies of the material found on Life-Enhancement.Com for personal use only. You must attach the following copyright to everything you copy:
©2018, Life Enhancement, Inc. All rights reserved.
Any violation of the Terms and Conditions immediately terminates your right to use the content contained in Life-Enhancement.Com and you are required to destroy all copies you have made of that content.
Liability
The use of the Life-Enhancement.Com and its content is at your own risk.
When using Life-Enhancement.Com, information is transmitted in ways beyond the control of Life-Enhancement.Com. Life Enhancement Products, Inc. assumes no liability for the delay, failure, interruption or corruption of any data or other information in connection with use of Life-Enhancement.Com.
The Life-Enhancement.Com web site and its content are provided "as is." Life Enhancement Products, Inc., its licensors, and its suppliers, to the fullest extent permitted by law, disclaim all warranties, either express or implied, statutory or otherwise, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, non-infringement of third parties' rights, and fitness for particular purpose. Specifically, Life Enhancement Products, Inc., its licensors and its suppliers make no representations or warranties about the following: The accuracy, reliability, completeness, or timeliness of the content, software, text, graphics, links, or communications provided on or through the use of Life-Enhancement.Com.
In no event shall Life Enhancement Products, Inc., its licensors, its suppliers or any third parties mentioned on Life-Enhancement.Com be liable for any damages, including but not limited to, incidental and consequential damages, personal injury, wrongful death, lost profits, damages resulting from lost data, business interruption resulting from the use or inability to use Life-Enhancement.Com or the content whether based on warranty, contract, tort or any other legal theory, and whether or not Life-Enhancement.Com is advised of the possibility of such damages. Life-Enhancement.Com is not liable for any personal injury, including death, caused by your use or misuse of this site, or it's content.
Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Life Enhancement Products, Inc., its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers, harmless from and against any claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements including without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your violation of these Terms and Conditions.
Jurisdiction
You expressly agree that exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute with Life Enhancement Products, Inc., or in any way relating to your use of Life-Enhancement.Com, resides in the courts of the State of California and you further agree and expressly consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of the State of California in connection with any such dispute including any claim involving Life Enhancement Products, Inc. or its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, officers, directors, telecommunication providers and content providers.
These Terms and Conditions are governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of California, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms and Conditions, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms and Conditions shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition.
Copyright
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips and software (unless otherwise noted) is the property of Life Enhancement Products, Inc. The reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance of the content on this site is strictly prohibited without prior written authorization.
Sign up for our Newsletter
Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
Our Products
Best Sellers
New Products
On Sale
About Life Enhancement
Login to Account
Call (800) 543-3873
*These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.
© 2020 Life Enhancement Products.
Powered by Shopify
